olweb.tv 2014-06-29

# Privacy - Watch Tv Online

By using this site, you agree to our Privacy Policy.  
If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use this site.  
we review this privacy policy periodically and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this policy at any time.  
This page should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes.   
If you want to communicate with us about our policy, please e-mail us at   

Online TV Media, which operates the Internet site located at [www.olweb.tv](http://www.olweb.tv/), recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about visitors to our sites. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address or email address, is automatically collected from visitors to our sites. Personally identifiable information about visitors to our sites is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. We may collect certain non-personal information to optimize our Web pages for your computer (i.e., the identity of your Internet browser, the type of operating system you use, your IP address and the domain name of your Internet service provider). We may use such non-personal information for internal purposes, including but not limited to improving the content of our sites.

In those instances when we do collect personally identifiable information, the following policies apply:

**Notice**

Online TV Media will notify you when we are collecting personally identifiable information about you and how we intend to use it. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with information you requested, in connection with entry forms, or in connection with community postings such as chat and bulletin boards. 

Sometimes Online TV Media engages in activities with business partners and sponsors with whom personal information is jointly collected or shared. We will try to make it clear at the time of collection who is asking for and/or sharing your information. In situations where your information will be shared, it is recommended that you also review the privacy policy of our business partner or sponsor.

**Use and Security**

Personally identifiable information that visitors submit to our sites is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted unless we disclose other uses in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. Such other uses may include sending you information or materials we think you will find interesting, or sharing the information with Online TV Media's Media's advertisers and reputable business partners. However, at the time of collection, you will have the option of instructing us not to send you additional information or share your personal information with third parties. Online TV Media is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of our business partners.

Online TV Media may use reputable third parties to manage activities available on our sites including, but not limited to statistical analysis, or chats. These parties may have access to personally identifiable information submitted by visitors who participate in those activities. Similarly, we may contract with third parties to handle the fulfillment of subscriptions or requests for information you submit to our sites, such as sending you a newsletter. In most instances, Online TV Media instructs these third parties to use personally identifiable information only for the specific purpose for which it is collected, and not to sell, market or transfer such information to other entities. If Online TV Media obtains personal information that has been collected from you by a third party, including our business partners, this Privacy Policy nonetheless governs Online TV Media's use of that information.

Please remember that any information posted on bulletin boards and/or communicated in chat areas becomes public information. You should use caution when sharing information as any of it can be collected and used by people you may not know. Users under the age of 18 should be particularly careful not to divulge any personal information. While Online TV Media strives to protect and respect your privacy, we can not guarantee the security of any information you disclose in a chat room or bulletin board and you do so at your own risk.

Online TV Media may use personally identifiable information in aggregate form to make our sites better and more responsive to the needs of our visitors. This statistical compilation and analysis of information may also be used by Online TV Media or provided to others, in aggregate, for marketing, advertising or research purposes.

If at any time after submitting your personal information to our sites you would no longer like to receive information from us, simply follow the "unsubscribe" directions at the end of any email communication you receive.

Online TV Media does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

Personal information may be disclosed in special situations where Online TV Media has reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with Online TV Media's rights, property, users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. Also, Online TV Media may reveal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

Online TV Media maintains appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personally identifiable information submitted to our sites, and periodically reviews and updates its security measures in light of current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. Although Online TV Media strives to protect your personal information, we can not ensure or warranty the security of any information you may transmit to us. This is done so at your own risk. Once we do receive your transmission, however, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

**Cookies**

Cookies are data that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard-drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are an industry standard used by most Web sites, including those operated by Online TV Media, can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site. They allow us to track usage patterns and to compile data that can help us improve our content and target advertising. Our Cookies are no programs that can cause damage to a user's systems or files. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature. But you should note that Cookies may be necessary to provide you with features such as adding your personal favourites.Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Online TV Media.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [_Google ad and content network privacy policy_](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html). 

**Links to Third Party and Co-Branded Sites**

Online TV Media has established many links directly to sites operated by third parties. These sites are not operated or maintained by Online TV Media. These sites may collect personal information from you. You should check the applicable privacy policy's of the third party site's in case you enter these sites. All links to external sites (not Online TV Media's) are opened in a new window! 

Online TV Media chooses its advertisers and business partners carefully. However, Online TV Media is not responsible for the content or practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site. These links are meant for the user's convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement or approval by Online TV Media of the content, policies or practices of such third party sites. Once you enter a third party site by such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site.
